let LemonBreezeQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "Which drinks use the blue tea?",
        "option1": "Violet Breeze and Strawberry Lemon Fizz",
        "option2": "Dragon Breeze and Acai Berry Spritz",
        "option3": "Pineapple Lemon Breeze and Peach Lemon Fizz",
        "option4": "Violet Breeze and Dragon Breeze",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a true statement?",
        "option1": "Our blue tea is caffeinated.",
        "option2": "Our blue tea is caffeine free.",
        "option3": "Our blue tea made of black tea.",
        "option4": "Our blue tea made of green tea.",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What makes our Strawberry Lemon Fizz and Peach Lemon Fizz 'fizzy'?",
        "option1": "We add sparkling water on the top of the drinks.",
        "option2": "We carbonate the entire drink to make it fizzy.",
        "option3": "We keep shaking the drink to make it fizzy.",
        "option4": "We make the entire drink with sparkling water.",
        "answer": 1
    },
      
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the tea leaf used to make our blue tea?",
        "option1": "Purple Pea Tea Flower",
        "option2": "Butterfly Pea Tea Flower",
        "option3": "Hibiscus Tea Flower",
        "option4": "Lavender Tea Flower",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is best to describe Lemon Breeze drinks?",
        "option1": "Not all of the Lemon Breeze drinks have 2 distinct layers.",
        "option2": "All of the Lemon Breeze drinks have no layers.",
        "option3": "All of the Lemon Breeze drinks have 2 distinct layers.",
        "option4": "Not all of the Lemon Breeze drinks have no layers.",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which 3 syrups used to make the Tropical Breeze?",
        "option1": "Peach, Lemon, and Kiwi.",
        "option2": "Fruit Tea, Lemon, and Kiwi.",
        "option3": "Passion Fruit, Lemon, and Kiwi.",
        "option4": "Pink Guava, Lemon, and Kiwi.",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recipe for a Regular size with no topping Violet Breeze?",
        "option1": "60% ice, 1.2 sugar, 1.0 lemon, 150cc water, and 500 line blue tea.",
        "option2": "60% ice, 1.0 sugar, 1.2 lemon, 150cc water, and 500 line blue tea.",
        "option3": "60% ice, 0.5 sugar, 1.8 lemon, 150cc water, and 500 line blue tea.",
        "option4": "60% ice, 0.8 sugar, 1.5 lemon, 150cc water, and 500 line blue tea.",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recipe for a Regular size with topping Dragon Breeze?",
        "option1": "50% ice, 0.3 sugar, 1.0 dragon fruit, 0.5 lemon, 50cc water, and 400 line blue tea.",
        "option2": "50% ice, 0.8 sugar, 1.5 dragon fruit, 1.0 lemon, 50cc water, and 400 line blue tea.",
        "option3": "50% ice, 0.25 sugar, 1.2 dragon fruit, 0.8 lemon, 50cc water, and 400 line blue tea.",
        "option4": "50% ice, 0.6 sugar, 1.8 dragon fruit, 1.2 lemon, 50cc water, and 400 line blue tea.",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you best describe Strawberry Lemon Fizz to the customer?",
        "option1": "It tastes like strawberry lemonade and fizzy.",
        "option2": "It tastes like strawberry flavor tea and fizzy.",
        "option3": "It tastes like strawberry lemonade.",
        "option4": "It tastes like strawberry flavor tea.",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How do we keep the blue tea stay seperated from the bottom layer in the drink?",
        "option1": "Having ice will help the blue tea stay on the top.",
        "option2": "Pour the blue tea slowly on the top of the drink.",
        "option3": "Make sure to not shake the cup after sealing the drink.",
        "option4": "All of the above.",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Can kids/customer who cannot drink caffeine order our lemon breeze drinks?",
        "option1": "They cannot because our blue tea in lemon breezes has black tea in it.",
        "option2": "They can because they can choose to not add blue tea in the lemon breeze drinks.",
        "option3": "They cannot because our blue tea in lemon breezes is caffeinated.",
        "option4": "They can because our blue tea in lemon breezes is caffeine free.",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which option below that incorrect to reply to the customer who want to order blended lemon breeze?",
        "option1": "Let customer know that our blended drinks located on frosty section.",
        "option2": "Let customer know that lemon breeze only comes over ice.",
        "option3": "Let customer know that they can only order it hot.",
        "option4": "All of the above are incorrect.",
        "answer": 3
    }
];